[
  {
    "name": "nine",
    "category": "NUMBER"
  },
  {
    "name": "major bank have join with fintech startup r3cev llc -lrb- r3 -rrb- to develop a framework for use",
    "category": "O"
  },
  {
    "name": "Blockchain",
    "category": "LOCATION"
  },
  {
    "name": "technology in financial market .",
    "category": "O"
  },
  {
    "name": "the announcement of the partnership to design and deliver advanced distributed/shared ledger technology to global financial market include some of the biggest name in global banking",
    "category": "O"
  },
  {
    "name": ", include",
    "category": "O"
  },
  {
    "name": "Barclays",
    "category": "ORGANIZATION"
  },
  {
    "name": ",",
    "category": "O"
  },
  {
    "name": "BBVA",
    "category": "ORGANIZATION"
  },
  {
    "name": ",",
    "category": "O"
  },
  {
    "name": "Commonwealth Bank of Australia",
    "category": "ORGANIZATION"
  },
  {
    "name": "-lrb- CBA -rrb-",
    "category": "O"
  },
  {
    "name": ",",
    "category": "O"
  },
  {
    "name": "Credit Suisse",
    "category": "ORGANIZATION"
  },
  {
    "name": ",",
    "category": "O"
  },
  {
    "name": "J.P. Morgan",
    "category": "ORGANIZATION"
  },
  {
    "name": ",",
    "category": "O"
  },
  {
    "name": "State Street",
    "category": "LOCATION"
  },
  {
    "name": ",",
    "category": "O"
  },
  {
    "name": "Royal Bank",
    "category": "ORGANIZATION"
  },
  {
    "name": "of",
    "category": "O"
  },
  {
    "name": "Scotland",
    "category": "LOCATION"
  },
  {
    "name": "and",
    "category": "O"
  },
  {
    "name": "UBS",
    "category": "ORGANIZATION"
  },
  {
    "name": ".",
    "category": "O"
  },
  {
    "name": "utilize the",
    "category": "O"
  },
  {
    "name": "Blockchain",
    "category": "LOCATION"
  },
  {
    "name": ", the digital ledger that underpin",
    "category": "O"
  },
  {
    "name": "Bitcoin",
    "category": "PERSON"
  },
  {
    "name": ", the group plan to collaborate on research",
    "category": "O"
  },
  {
    "name": ", experimentation",
    "category": "O"
  },
  {
    "name": ", design",
    "category": "O"
  },
  {
    "name": ", and engineering with a aim of deliver advanced state-of-the-art enterprise-scale share ledger solution that also meet banking requirement for security",
    "category": "O"
  },
  {
    "name": ", reliability",
    "category": "O"
  },
  {
    "name": ", performance",
    "category": "O"
  },
  {
    "name": ", scalability",
    "category": "O"
  },
  {
    "name": ", and audit .",
    "category": "O"
  },
  {
    "name": "lead by r3",
    "category": "O"
  },
  {
    "name": ", the group will establish collaborative joint working group to develop these effort ; many",
    "category": "O"
  },
  {
    "name": ", if not all of its member have",
    "category": "O"
  },
  {
    "name": "previously",
    "category": "DATE"
  },
  {
    "name": "work on way of use the",
    "category": "O"
  },
  {
    "name": "Blockchain",
    "category": "LOCATION"
  },
  {
    "name": "in everyday business",
    "category": "O"
  },
  {
    "name": ", with the likes of the CBA work on",
    "category": "O"
  },
  {
    "name": "Blockchain",
    "category": "LOCATION"
  },
  {
    "name": "financial settlement",
    "category": "O"
  },
  {
    "name": ", and",
    "category": "O"
  },
  {
    "name": "Barclays",
    "category": "ORGANIZATION"
  },
  {
    "name": "even go as far as accept Bitcoin payment .",
    "category": "O"
  },
  {
    "name": "Kevin Hanley",
    "category": "PERSON"
  },
  {
    "name": ", Director of Design at",
    "category": "O"
  },
  {
    "name": "Royal Bank of Scotland",
    "category": "ORGANIZATION"
  },
  {
    "name": "explain why the group be come together",
    "category": "O"
  },
  {
    "name": ", say in a statement",
    "category": "O"
  },
  {
    "name": "right now",
    "category": "DATE"
  },
  {
    "name": "you be see significant money and time be spend on exploration of these technology in a fractured way that lack the strategic",
    "category": "O"
  },
  {
    "name": ", coordinate vision so critical to timely success .",
    "category": "O"
  },
  {
    "name": "the r3 model be change the game .",
    "category": "O"
  },
  {
    "name": "the collaborative model we have establish with r3 and the other bank be a very effective way to deliver robust shared ledger solution to the financial service sector",
    "category": "O"
  },
  {
    "name": ", he say .",
    "category": "O"
  },
  {
    "name": "save money cut out the middleman in financial transaction be all about save money",
    "category": "O"
  },
  {
    "name": ", and that be what implementation of the Blockchain would mean for these big bank",
    "category": "O"
  },
  {
    "name": ", let alone the fact that Blockchain transaction be quicker and more secure as well .",
    "category": "O"
  },
  {
    "name": "these new technology could transform how financial transaction be record",
    "category": "O"
  },
  {
    "name": ", reconcile and report ... senior Vice President and head of emerge Technologies at",
    "category": "O"
  },
  {
    "name": "State Street Hu Liang",
    "category": "LOCATION"
  },
  {
    "name": "add",
    "category": "O"
  },
  {
    "name": ", ... all with additional security",
    "category": "O"
  },
  {
    "name": ", lower error rate and significant cost reduction .",
    "category": "O"
  },
  {
    "name": "the step to work together on the implementation of the",
    "category": "O"
  },
  {
    "name": "Blockchain",
    "category": "LOCATION"
  },
  {
    "name": "in financial market be logical as bank and other financial institution would need to agree to standard eventually",
    "category": "O"
  },
  {
    "name": ", so it make sense that some of the big name would be involve collaboratively in develop those standard .",
    "category": "O"
  },
  {
    "name": "there be no time frame give by the group in term of target",
    "category": "O"
  },
  {
    "name": ", however in theory work together on the Blockchain could see the platform takeover financial market even quicker than many have already expect .",
    "category": "O"
  }
]